So, let me show you one of the one of the security mechanism called wind digest is an authentication.
Let us see authentication, a later protocol, especially.
So if you modify this W digest key, probably it's like if you enable the W digest key, your
windows operating system will be saving the credentials in a plain text inside the
memory.
So, you don't need to crack any hashes or you don't need to brute force a hashes using
the hashcat or anything.
So, you can view, you can see the credentials in a plain text, okay, if this key get enabled,
okay.
So, often the threat factors will be modifying this key for privileges, relations or
getting the credentials from the machine, okay.
So, let me, before executing that, let me query the, in digest key.
And let me check if it's already enabled or not.
The system was unable to find the specific registry key.
Let me redirect to the directory editor, local machine, system current control set, control
set, let me check the security providers.
And here we have, here we have a security window just and user control key has been the
value of the user log and credentials was one just I marked it previously and let me copy
it here and I will be, I will query now, so now you can see the user log on plain shell
has been logged in 0x1 and it's the values one basically, you can check it from here.
But threat factors will be, default in Windows it will be disabled, okay, it will be the
value will be 0 here instead of one in a default, but the threat factors will be enabling
this W digest because of, I already said the credentials username and password will be saved
in a plain text instead of instead of an encryption, so we don't need to crack any hashtag
or anything using different tools, so it will be pretty easy to see the credentials in
a plain text, okay.
So now the key has been modified into one and it was being successfully created executed, so
the user log on plain shell has changed to 0 in one, the USB has been enabled because
I enabled a few weeks before, yeah, hopefully it's a best this to this thing to learn
in a threat investigation view, okay, so let's stop off and we'll continue our discussion
in our next video, see you guys, bye bye.